<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>

    <integer-array name="tourist_places_images">
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_pyramids_and_camels</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_egyptian_museum_mummified_monkey</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_al_azhar_mosque</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_hanging_church_interior</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_perfume_shop_in_khan_el_khalili</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_muhammad_ali_mosque_on_the_citadel</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_sultan_hassan_mosque</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_view_from_the_top_of_bab_zuweila</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_architectural_detail_in_madrassa</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_ibn_tulun_mosque</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_the_cairo_tower</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_roda_island_nilometer</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_mosque_of_al_hakim</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_cairo_the_cairo_tower</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_saqqara_step_pyramid_of_djoser</item>
        <item>@drawable/chaar_hachamaim_synagogue_cairo</item>
    </integer-array>

    <array name="tourist_places_names">
        <item>Pyramids of Giza</item>
        <item>The Egyptian Museum</item>
        <item>Al-Azhar Mosque</item>
        <item>Old Cairo (Coptic Cairo)</item>
        <item>Khan el-Khalili (Souq Quarter)</item>
        <item>The Citadel</item>
        <item>Sultan Hassan Mosque</item>
        <item>Bab Zuweila</item>
        <item>Al-Muizz li-Din Allah Street</item>
        <item>Ibn Tulun Mosque</item>
        <item>Zamalek</item>
        <item>Roda Island</item>
        <item>Mosque of Al-Hakim</item>
        <item>Downtown Cairo</item>
        <item>Saqqara</item>
        <item>Chaar Hachamaim Synagogue</item>
    </array>
    <array name="tourist_places_description">
        <item>The Pyramids of Giza are Cairo\'s number one half-day trip and a must-do attraction on
            everyone\'s itinerary. Right on the edge of the city, these fourth dynasty funerary
            temples have been wowing travelers for centuries and continue to be one of the country\'s
            major highlights. Despite the heat, the dust, and the tourist hustle, you can\'t miss
            a trip here.</item>
        <item>The absolutely staggering collection of antiquities displayed in Cairo\'s
            Egyptian Museum makes it one of the world\'s great museums.
            You would need a lifetime to see everything on show. The museum was
            founded in 1857 by French Egyptologist August Mariette and moved to its
            current home - in the distinctive powder-pink mansion in Downtown Cairo - in 1897.</item>
        <item>Al-Azhar Mosque is the finest building of Cairo\'s Fatimid era, and one of the city\'s
            earliest surviving mosques, completed in AD 972. It\'s also one of the world\'s oldest
            universities.</item>
        <item>This small church-filled cluster of twisty laneways lies within the walls of
            Old Babylon where the Roman Emperor Trajan first built a fortress along the Nile.
            Parts of the Roman towers still preside over the main street.</item>
        <item>Khan el-Khalili is one of the world\'s great shopping experiences.
            This Middle Eastern souq (bazaar) is a labyrinthine collection of
            skinny alleyways established as a shopping district in AD 1400 that
            still rings with the clang of metal workers and silversmiths.</item>
        <item>In a commanding location at the foot of the Mokattam Hills, Cairo\'s citadel
            was built by Saladin in 1176.</item>
        <item>One of the finest examples of Mamluk architecture in the world, Sultan Hassan Mosque
            is a vision of Arabic artistry with an abundance of stalactite detailing and
            intricate arabesque features. It was built in 1356-63 for the Sultan Hassan el-Nasir.</item>
        <item>Of all the Islamic Cairo district\'s gates, Bab Zuweila is the most interesting.
            You can climb to the top of this medieval era relic (built in the 11th century)
            for some amazing rooftop views over Islamic Cairo.</item>
        <item>The northern section of Al-Muizz li-Din Allah Street is rimmed by
            fine Mamluk buildings that have been painstakingly restored to their former glory.
            The Madrassa of as-Salih Ayyub, built in 1247, is a showcase of the tranquil
            simplicity of Islamic architecture.</item>
        <item>The second oldest mosque still standing in Cairo, Ibn Tulun Mosque,
            was built between AD 876 and 879 and modeled on the Kaaba in Mecca (Saudi Arabia).
            At the time it was built, it was the largest mosque in existence.</item>
        <item>The Nile island of Gezira is home to the district of Zamalek and the majority of Cairo\'s arty
            boutiques and hipster restaurants. Dating from the mid 19th century, the entire area has a distinctly
            European feel to its architecture with wide boulevards rimmed by Jacaranda trees and splendidly
            ornate Belle Époque mansions (many of which are now home to various embassies).</item>
        <item>Lovely Roda Island - just south of Gezira Island - is home to Monastirli Palace,
            once the residence of an Ottoman pasha. Inside the palace gardens, right at the
            island\'s southern tip, is Cairo\'s Nilometer - that was used to measure the ebb and
            flow of the Nile and predict the annual flood heights.</item>
        <item>Caliph Al-Hakim is one of the most fascinating rulers of Egypt. This Fatimid leader was
            renowned for his terrifying rule over the land, which included frequent murders of his royal
            household staff, nightly patrols of the streets of his city dressed incognito on a donkey to make
            sure his subjects were behaving themselves, and issuing bizarre rulings across the country
            (such as banning the eating of the Egyptian mallow-leaf called molokheya because only he wanted
            to be able to consume it).</item>
        <item>If you want to capture a sense of late 19th-century Cairo when the city was nicknamed
            the "Paris of the East" take a stroll through the downtown district with your gaze diverted up
            at the car-exhaust blackened architecture rather than on the bedlam at street level.</item>
        <item>The vast necropolis of Saqqara is home to the "other pyramids" and a day trip out here
            is just as rewarding as a trip to Giza\'s pyramids.
            Location: 30 kms south of Cairo</item>
        <item>The Synagogue is an incredible example of the diversity of architecture in Cairo and
            represents a myriad of different styles (Baroque, Art Deco) in bas relief with
            overlays of Pharonic Art. </item>
    </array>

    <integer-array name="hotel_images">
        <item>@drawable/golden_boat_foating</item>
        <item>@drawable/almasah_hotel_and_spa</item>
        <item>@drawable/cataract_pyramids_resort</item>
        <item>@drawable/le_passage_cairo_hotel_casino</item>
        <item>@drawable/the_gabriel_boutique_hotel</item>
        <item>@drawable/pyramids_park_resort_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/dusit_thani_lakeview_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/renaissance_cairo_mirage_city_hotel</item>
        <item>@drawable/fairmont_nile_city</item>
        <item>@drawable/grand_nile_tower_</item>
        <item>@drawable/kempinski_nile_hotel_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/safir_hotel_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/cairo_marriott_hotel_omar_khayyam_casino</item>
        <item>@drawable/mena_house_hotel</item>
        <item>@drawable/radisson_blu_hotel</item>
        <item>@drawable/fairmont_heliopolis_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/concorde_elsalam_hotel_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/fairmont_towers_heliopolis</item>
        <item>@drawable/sonesta_hotel_tower_casino_cairo</item>
    </integer-array>

    <array name="hotel_names">
        <item>Golden Boat Floating Hotel</item>
        <item>Al Masah Hotel And Spa</item>
        <item>Cataract Pyramids Resort</item>
        <item>Le Passage Cairo Hotel Casino</item>
        <item>The Gabriel Boutique Hotel</item>
        <item>Pyramids Park Resort Cairo</item>
        <item>Dusit Thani LakeView Cairo</item>
        <item>Renaissance Cairo Mirage City Hotel</item>
        <item>Fairmont Nile City</item>
        <item>Grand Nile Tower (Formerly Grand Hyatt Cairo)</item>
        <item>Kempinski Nile Hotel, Cairo</item>
        <item>Safir Hotel Cairo</item>
        <item>Cairo Marriott Hotel Omar Khayyam Casino</item>
        <item>Mena House Hotel (Formerly Mena House Oberoi)</item>
        <item>Radisson Blu Hotel, Cairo Heliopolis</item>
        <item>Fairmont Heliopolis Cairo</item>
        <item>Concorde El Salam Hotel Cairo</item>
        <item>Fairmont Towers, Heliopolis</item>
        <item>Sonesta Hotel Tower Casino Cairo</item>
    </array>
    <array name="hotel_descriptions">
        <item>Overlooking the Nile and the Pyramids of Giza, this 5-star floating hotel features
            free Wi-Fi, an outdoor pool and a sundeck with a bar. It is 5 minutes? walk from local
            shopping outlets. A minibar, satellite TV and safety deposit box are equipped in all of
            Golden Boat Floating Hotel?s units.</item>
        <item>Al Masah Hotel and Spa features a terrace with a swimming pool. Located in the green area of
            Nasr City, it offers 5 restaurants and a wellness centre. All the elegant rooms have a balcony.
            All the rooms and suites at Al Masah have views of the terrace, the garden or the pool.</item>
        <item>Featuring views of the great Pyramids, this resort on the edge of Cairo offers a charming
            pool garden. Its 5 dining options include a buffet restaurant with live piano music.
            The air-conditioned rooms at Cataract Pyramids are spacious and equipped with satellite
            TVs and minibars.</item>
        <item>Le Passage Cairo is only 2-minutes from the Cairo International Airport in Cairo?s
            Heliopolis district. The hotel offers fine restaurants, a discotheque and a casino.</item>
        <item>Situated in one of Cairo s affluent districts- Heliopolis, the Gabriel?s design is
            inspired by classical era and is decorated with warm colours. It offers modern
            accommodation with free Wi-Fi, an outdoor pool and a retail arcade.</item>
        <item>Pyramids Park Resort Cairo is set in 25 acres of gardens, just 5 minutes drive from
            the Pyramids. It has a 1750 square metre pool and all its rooms have balconies.
            All the rooms at Pyramids Park are air conditioned and cable TV.</item>
        <item>This stylish and contemporary 5-star hotel, situated in New Cairo, offers luxurious
            accommodation in a sanctuary of tranquillity with an excellent location setting.
            Dusit Thani is only about a 20-minute drive from Cairo Airport. It has easy access
            to many tourist attractions</item>
        <item>Featuring luxury accommodation with free Wi-Fi, this 5-star hotel is located 10 minutes?
            drive from Cairo International Airport. It boasts a pool, fitness centre and restaurant.
            Heliopolis is 10 minutes away by car. Furnished with an elegant décor</item>
        <item>Located in the Nile City Towers by the River Nile, this 5-star hotel features a rooftop
            pool deck with spectacular views across Cairo to the Pyramids. It offers 8 food and beverage
            venues. All of this Fairmont Hotel?s soundproofed rooms are decorated with elegant Art Deco
            furnishings.</item>
        <item>Luxurious rooms and suites offer views across the River Nile at Grand Nile Tower on
            Roda Island. The wellness centre also overlooks the Nile and the resort features 8
            restaurants and an outdoor pool. The elegantly decorated rooms and suites at Grand Nile
            Tower come with a work desk, satellite TV and minibar.</item>
        <item>Situated in Cairo\'s affluent Garden City district, Kempinski Hotel offers luxurious
            rooms on the shores of the Nile River. It features a wellness centre and a rooftop
            swimming pool. Each of Kempinski\'s rooms is fitted with soundproofed windows, free Wi-Fi
            and high definition LCD TVs with satellite channels.</item>
        <item>A 10-minute walk from the Nile River embankment, Safir hotel in Cairo\'s city centre
            offers luxurious rooms with balconies. It features an outdoor pool, gym and free Wi-Fi
            in public areas. Each air-conditioned room is spacious and includes a work desk,
            satellite TV and minibar.</item>
        <item>Located in Cairo\'s Zamalek district, the Marriott Omar Khayyam offers luxurious rooms
            with a balcony. It features an outdoor swimming pool, a casino and 14 food and beverage
            outlets. All guest rooms at the Cairo Marriott feature satellite TV, a minibar, tea/coffee
            facilities and elegant bathrooms.</item>
        <item>Overlooking the Great Pyramids of Giza, this hotel is surrounded by 40 acres of green
            gardens and has a spa, fitness centre and a pool. The rooms are decorated with handcrafted
            furniture. All accommodations at Mena House Hotel have air conditioning and include
            luxurious fabrics, a seating area and LCD TV.</item>
        <item>Located in Cairo?s stylish Heliopolis district, the 5-star Radisson Blu offers
            a rooftop pool with panoramic Cairo views. It has an extensive daily breakfast
            buffet, free Wi-Fi and in-room LCD TVs. Guest rooms at Radisson Blu Hotel Cairo
            Heliopolis feature modern décor, Select Comfort beds and a seating area.</item>
        <item>Fairmont Heliopolis features 3 tennis courts, and a hot tub. It has 3 swimming pools
            surrounded by a landscaped garden. Free Wi-Fi is available in all rooms. All rooms
            feature touches of Egyptian heritage in their décor. Each air-conditioned rooms has
            flat-screen TV, a minibar and a work desk.</item>
        <item>Just a 25-minute drive from City Centre, Concorde El Salam Hotel Cairo is 6 km from
            fashionable Heliopolis suburb. It features 9 restaurants, 2 outdoor pools, and private
            stables. The rooms include flat-screen TVs and free Wi-Fi.</item>
        <item>Situated in the Heliopolis neighbourhood, this 5-star hotel is a 10-minute drive from
            Cairo Airport. It has 3 swimming pools, a modern fitness centre, and spacious rooms with
            luxury bedding. Rooms at Fairmont Towers have parquet floors and floor-to-ceiling windows
            with city and garden views.</item>
        <item>Located in Nasr City residential area and a 10-minute drive from the airport, Sonesta
            Hotel boasts 5 restaurants and 4 bars. It features an outdoor swimming pool and sun terrace.
            All air-conditioned rooms at the Sonesta Hotel Tower and Casino Cairo are spacious and
            elegantly decorated.</item>
    </array>

    <integer-array name="parks_images">
        <item>@drawable/nile_river_garden</item>
        <item>@drawable/alazhar_park_in_my_guid</item>
        <item>@drawable/zamalek_gezira_island</item>
        <item>@drawable/nilemeter_garden</item>
        <item>@drawable/wadi_degla_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/mokkatom_mountain_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/egypt_western_desert</item>
        <item>@drawable/japanese_garden_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/gize_zoo_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/international_equestrian_club_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/sayyed_zeinab_cultural_park_cairo</item>
        <item>@drawable/gabalaya_park_and_aquarium_cairo</item>
    </integer-array>

    <array name="parks_names">
        <item>Nile River</item>
        <item>Al-Azhar Park</item>
        <item>Zamalek (Gezira Island)</item>
        <item>Nilometer</item>
        <item>Wadi Degla</item>
        <item>Mokkatom Mountain</item>
        <item>Western Desert</item>
        <item>Japanese Garden</item>
        <item>Giza Zoo</item>
        <item>International Equestrian Club</item>
        <item>Sayyed Zeinab Cultural Park</item>
        <item>Gabalaya Park and Aquarium</item>
    </array>
    <array name="parks_descriptions">
        <item>The Nile River is simply everything you expect it to be! Gorgeous and large,
            it is bound to take your breath away and show you how amazing nature is.</item>
        <item>it\'s a very beautiful well organized park, it has a variety of roses, flowers and trees
            , and with some soft music at night which makes it so romantic , the restaurant studio Masr
            is a great value to the place with it\'s Islamic architecture style which build with stones
            , and the food is amazing , if you sit at the terrace you can see the magnificent citadel
            with Mohamed Ali mosque on top of it and great sultan Hassan mosque and Madrasa with
            it\'s 84 m high minaret all these gives you a great skyline.</item>
        <item>This island is located in the Nile River between downtown Cairo and Giza,
            and is characterized by upscale hotels, restaurants and pleasant gardens.</item>
        <item>It really is - it is quiet, calm, a nice little park, shady, and the breeze from the
            Nile is fabulous.</item>
        <item>Just a few minutes from chaotic Cairo traffic, you can find this treasure of nature.
        Easy to rich by taxi, entrance 5 le for foreigners, if you want to enter by car you will
        pay 10 le. There is possibility to overnight in tent. You can consider this
            as five billion stars hotel</item>
        <item>We went there at night.. There are some cafés and restaurants with a great view of the city..
            The view at night is amazing..</item>
        <item>We found Djed Egypt Travel to take us on a 6 days desert safari in Western Desert.
            Guide and drivers were enchanting. We enjoyed their attention and brilliant cooking.</item>
        <item>This is a beautiful theme garden near the edge of what once was a beautiful winter
            escape from Cairo.</item>
        <item>the zoo is so big, has lots type of animals lions, Indian and African elephants,
            nile crocodiles, seals, lion sea, polar bear, bears, white rhino,
            giraffes, monkeys, camels. Very nice place to visit, i ,love animal life and this zoo
            is full of it, we had our private guide and he made things easy for us, it is a place
            to go again.</item>
        <item>To enjoy horse racing and international horse racing, you should visit this place</item>
        <item>one of the best heritage islamic places</item>
        <item>This place used to be the pleasant Gabalaya Park and Aquarium, that landscaped gardens
            with aquariums set in rocks (though not many actual fish), however. </item>
    </array>

    <integer-array name="resturants_images">
        <item>@drawable/pizza_king</item>
        <item>@drawable/momen</item>
        <item>@drawable/sahraan</item>
        <item>@drawable/papa_johns_pizza</item>
        <item>@drawable/mcdonalds</item>
        <item>@drawable/shawerma_elreem</item>
        <item>@drawable/spectra</item>
        <item>@drawable/cook_door</item>
        <item>@drawable/shuffle</item>
        <item>@drawable/prego</item>
        <item>@drawable/manaeesh_elreem</item>
        <item>@drawable/elhorany_seafood</item>
        <item>@drawable/tarweeah</item>
        <item>@drawable/aldahan</item>
        <item>@drawable/baladina_</item>
        <item>@drawable/buffalo_burger</item>
        <item>@drawable/burger_king</item>
        <item>@drawable/kfc</item>
        <item>@drawable/arabiata_al_shabrawy</item>
        <item>@drawable/elhattab_elsouri</item>
        <item>@drawable/koshary_sayed_hanafy</item>
    </integer-array>

    <array name="resturants_names">
        <item>Pizza King</item>
        <item>Mo\'men</item>
        <item>Sahraan</item>
        <item>Papa John\'s Pizza</item>
        <item>McDonald’s</item>
        <item>Shawerma El Reem</item>
        <item>Spectra</item>
        <item>Cook Door</item>
        <item>Shuffle</item>
        <item>Prego</item>
        <item>Manaeesh El Reem</item>
        <item>El Horany Seafood</item>
        <item>Tarweeah</item>
        <item>Al Dahan</item>
        <item>Baladina </item>
        <item>Buffalo Burger</item>
        <item>Burger King</item>
        <item>KFC</item>
        <item>Arabiata Al-Shabrawy</item>
        <item>El Hattab El Souri</item>
        <item>Koshary Sayed Hanafy</item>
    </array>

    <array name="resturants_address">
        <item>Address:Faisal</item>
        <item>Address:Faisal</item>
        <item>Address:6th of October - Central Axis</item>
        <item>Address:Haram</item>
        <item>Address:Faisal</item>
        <item>Address:Hadayek El Ahram</item>
        <item>Address:Hadayek Al Ahram</item>
        <item>Address:El Marioutia</item>
        <item>Address:Hadayek El Ahram</item>
        <item>Address:Faisal</item>
        <item>Address:Haram</item>
        <item>Address:Giza</item>
        <item>Address:Mansoureya Street</item>
        <item>Address:Mohandiseen</item>
        <item>Address:Al Wahat Road</item>
        <item>Address:Ard El Golf</item>
        <item>Address:Tivoli Dome</item>
        <item>Address:Heliopolis</item>
        <item>Address:Roxi</item>
        <item>Address:Nasr City</item>
        <item>Address:Nasr City</item>
    </array>

</resources>
